<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guides on Nice Polar Blog</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/categories/guides/</link><description>Recent content in Guides on Nice Polar Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://1hiking.github.io/categories/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A quick change to featured posts in Hugo</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2022/01/a-quick-change-to-featured-posts-in-hugo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2022/01/a-quick-change-to-featured-posts-in-hugo/</guid><description>I have been recently looking about how to add latests posts in my index page, since it has a giant space that has no purpose. I quickly glanced at this article by Damien in which he shared this snippet of code:
{{ range first 3 ( where .Site.Pages &amp;#34;Type&amp;#34; &amp;#34;in&amp;#34; site.Params.mainSections )}} ... {{ end }} However, it should add .Site.RegularPages instead of .Site.Pages because as the Hugo documentation states, .</description></item><item><title>A nice table of contents</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2022/01/a-nice-table-of-contents/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2022/01/a-nice-table-of-contents/</guid><description>Until now, I have used the following snippet to make a table of contents.
&amp;lt;div class=&amp;#34;toc&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Table of Contents&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; {{- .Page.TableOfContents }} &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt; However, when you have a lot of sections it becomes a bit annoying for the visitor to scroll to read.
An easy solution would be to use JS to detect a click and expand the table, or using CSS :hover events but in each case you will add unnecessary complexity as the project grows.</description></item><item><title>VS Code privacy settings</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2021/12/vs-code-privacy-settings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2021/12/vs-code-privacy-settings/</guid><description>Table of Contents Deprecated settings New telemetry settings Settings you might want to check Wrapping it up In contrast to some popular beliefs, it is possible to make VS Code a very private code editor without the need of using forks such as VSCodium.
Deprecated settings 🔗 The settings &amp;quot;telemetry.enableCrashReporter&amp;quot;: false and &amp;quot;telemetry.enableTelemetry&amp;quot;: false are deprecated and useless.
New telemetry settings 🔗 &amp;quot;telemetry.telemetryLevel&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;off&amp;quot; will disable all telemetry and crash reporting.</description></item><item><title>Matrix 101 for your friends</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2021/07/matrix-101-for-your-friends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2021/07/matrix-101-for-your-friends/</guid><description>Table of Contents Terminology Server and Guilds Homeservers and their relationship with Matrix Clients and their relationship with Element Homeservers What server to pick Self-hosting Migrating from your server Clients Alternative clients Encryption keys Some leaving notes Didn&amp;rsquo;t quite get it all? Read the official FAQ In recent years the Matrix protocol, messaging service, decentralised conversation store or whatever you want to call it has been gaining a lot of traction as a replacement in many communities for many reasons, it might be because IRC isn&amp;rsquo;t cutting it or you are using a service which doesn&amp;rsquo;t respect your privacy or has horrible security.</description></item><item><title>Making a browser from Scratch!</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2021/04/making-a-browser-from-scratch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/posts/2021/04/making-a-browser-from-scratch/</guid><description>Table of Contents Introduction Requirements Conclusions Inspired by Introduction 🔗 So let&amp;rsquo;s talk about developing a browser, one of the most complex programs in your computer!
As most people know, since the 90&amp;rsquo;s web browsers have been an essential program in anyone&amp;rsquo;s computer, they allow you to connect with your friends online, play videogames, read scientific papers, or even niche functions to connect to FTP&amp;hellip;! oh actually nevermind.</description></item></channel></rss>