<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Matrix on Nice Polar Blog</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/categories/matrix/</link><description>Recent content in Matrix on Nice Polar Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://1hiking.github.io/categories/matrix/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New theme New year</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/2021/12/new-theme-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/2021/12/new-theme-new-year/</guid><description>It has been a while since I have posted anything, however it has not been without a reason since I have done a Hugo theme for my own website! (and anyone really).
One of the key aspects over the change were some features I didn&amp;rsquo;t have in the last one, for example, a Table of Contents and had other features that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t using and added size to the page such as Google Analytics.</description></item><item><title>Matrix Stickers</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/2021/09/matrix-stickers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/2021/09/matrix-stickers/</guid><description>Table of Contents
The m.room.message &amp;ldquo;hack&amp;rdquo; The real method: m.sticker Implementation examples The Future of Stickers You possibly don&amp;rsquo;t know matrix stickers. e I have collected over these past few months some JSON&amp;rsquo;s, curiously I have found 2 types of &amp;ldquo;stickers&amp;rdquo;, so I will share and discuss them. Moreover I will also explain how some clients implement stickers.
Let&amp;rsquo;s open the dev console!
The m.room.message &amp;ldquo;hack&amp;rdquo; 🔗 This type of sticker is more of a inline message, you probably have seen this variant if a room has a discord bridge bot and users in the Discord room post custom emojis.</description></item><item><title>Matrix 101 for your friends</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/2021/07/matrix-101-for-your-friends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/2021/07/matrix-101-for-your-friends/</guid><description>Table of Contents
Terminology Server and Guilds Homeservers and their relationship with Matrix Clients and their relationship with Element Homeservers What server to pick Self-hosting Migrating from your server Clients Alternative clients Encryption keys Some leaving notes Didn&amp;rsquo;t quite get it all? Read the official FAQ In recent years the Matrix protocol, messaging service, decentralised conversation store or whatever you want to call it has been gaining a lot of traction as a replacement in many communities for many reasons, it might be because IRC isn&amp;rsquo;t cutting it or you are using a service which doesn&amp;rsquo;t respect your privacy or has horrible security.</description></item></channel></rss>