<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lists on Nice Polar Blog</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/lists/</link><description>Recent content in Lists on Nice Polar Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://1hiking.github.io/lists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Security, privacy and cryptography</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/lists/security-privacy-and-cryptography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/lists/security-privacy-and-cryptography/</guid><description>Table of Contents
Browsers Ungoogled-Chromium Firefox Browser extensions (also known as addons) Cryptography Miscellaneous PGP, Email and the family Open/Closed Source beliefs This page collects many URLs which write about various topics about security, privacy, cryptography, etc, or in the same way I do, collect more websites to validate their arguments for or against a technology or an ideology. I have no affiliation with none of these sites and I just maintain it for my own pleasure.</description></item><item><title>Hiking's curated list of F-droid apps</title><link>https://1hiking.github.io/lists/hikings-curated-list-of-f-droid-apps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://1hiking.github.io/lists/hikings-curated-list-of-f-droid-apps/</guid><description>Table of Contents
Browsers File managers Images, Music and Videos Document Viewers EXIF / Metadata editors F-droid clients RSS clients E-mail clients Password Manager Social Media clients (Reddit, Facebook, etc) Keyboards Launchers &amp;amp; Icon Packs 2FA Games No category A curated list of some worth checking applications in the F-droid repo (and others too), short descriptions and notes are listed below.
This list is low-maintainance mode, since the purpose of this list is to give you a taste of high-quality programs&amp;hellip; I believe there is a problem in F-droid in how they index and promote content in the front page, making harder for the user to find anything useful for their needs.</description></item></channel></rss>